{"data":[{"question":"John was the only one ___ I had invited.","a":"which","b":"that","c":"whom","d":"who","answer":"2","explain":"- \"Who\" is a Subject Pronoun (do an action)\u00a0\n- \"Whom\" is an Object Pronoun (receive an action) \n- That normally refers to things but it may refer to a class or type of person. \n- Which: used to ask or talk about one or more members of a group of people or things, when you are uncertain about it or about them \n+ We prefer which when the number of choices is limited","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"62","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"He arrived half an hour late,___ annoyed us very much.","a":"that","b":"as","c":"which","d":"what","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Which: used after a comma in writing, to add more information about the thing, situation, or event you have just mentioned","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"62","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"They are the boys ___ I went to school with.","a":"what","b":"where","c":"when","d":"whom","answer":"4","explain":"\n- When (=in\/on which): refers to a time expression \n- Where (=in\/at which): refers to a place \n- Why (= for which): refers to a reason \n- Whom: object pronoun for people, especially in non-defining relative clauses (in defining relative clauses we colloquially prefer who)","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"62","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"Who is it? \"This is the actress ___ his father claims seduced his son!","a":"who","b":"whom","c":"whose","d":"which","answer":"1","explain":"\n- \"Who\" is a Subject Pronoun (do an action) \n- \"Whom\" is an Object Pronoun (receive an action) \n- \"Whose\" is a Possessive Pronoun (Possessive forms tell us the person something belongs to) \n- Which: used to ask or talk about one or more members of a group of people or things, when you are uncertain about it or about them \n- We prefer which when the number of choices is limited","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"62","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"Do you like this tie? \"I prefer the one ___\"","a":"which is on the counter","b":"is on the counter","c":"which it is on the counter","d":"which on the counter","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Which: used to ask or talk about one or more members of a group of people or things, when you are uncertain about it or about them \n+We prefer which when the number of choices is limited \n- Which plays the role as a subject ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"62","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"Thank you very much for ___ you have done for my sister.","a":"that","b":"which","c":"it","d":"what","answer":"4","explain":"-That normally refers to things but it may refer to a class or type of person.\n- What: \u00a0used to introduce a clause about something that is or was not known or not certain\n+ What is preferred when the number of choices is unlimited\n- Which: used to ask or talk about one or more members of a group of people or things, when you are uncertain about it or about them\n+We prefer which when the number of choices is limited","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"62","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"He had no other desire ___ to make a fortune.","a":"but","b":"than","c":"except","d":"as","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Other than: apart from a particular person or thing [= except]","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"62","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"Most of his rich acquaintances ignored him, ___ is the way of their world.","a":"so","b":"as","c":"that","d":"what","answer":"2","explain":"\n- As: in the way that someone says or that something happens, or in the condition something is in","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"62","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"Joe believed without question ___ in his daily newspaper.","a":"about what he read","b":"of what he read","c":"whatever he read","d":"whenever he read","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Whatever: any or all of the things that are wanted, needed, or possible ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"62","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"The doctor will speak to ___ comes in first.","a":"whoever","b":"whomever","c":"whichever","d":"whatever","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Whoever: used to say that it does not matter who does something, is in a particular place \n- Whichever: used to say that it does not matter which thing or person is chosen because the result will be the same \n- Whatever:any or all of the things that are wanted, needed, or possible","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"62","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"}]}